Guide to the Reston Association records, 1964-2006
George Mason University Libraries
Special Collections and Archives, George Mason University
Reston Association records
1964-2006
George Mason University. Special Collections and Archives.
Reston Association
C0112
27 linear feet 54 boxes
The Reston Association records include meeting minutes, budgets, clippings, reports, handbooks, correspondence, and general information on the association. Also included is a series of photography, which has photographs, contact sheets, slides, and negatives. The collection documents the activities of the Reston Home Owners Association, later renamed Reston Association in 1987 to include apartments and condos. The collection covers the period of time from the 1964 to 2006.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open to research.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Karen Monagen on November 9, 2007 and by Charles D. McGuire in December 1994.
Historical Information
Reston is a planned community in Northern Virginia. Robert E. Simon, Jr., the founder of Reston, purchased the land with the proceeds from the sale of Carnegie Hall in New York City in 1961. Construction began in 1963 with the building of Lake Anne. Simon wanted Reston to be a place where individuals could remain their entire lives, thus many different types of housing were constructed. The focus of Reston, according to Simon, was to develop a place where people could live and work. Essentially he wanted Reston to be a way to live. A priority of this way of life was leisure time, so a wide variety of recreational choices were made available. In 1967, Gulf Oil Corporation formed a subsidiary, Reston Gulf, Inc. and took complete financial and operational control. During the next year, Reston construction proceeded at a quicker pace and the population grew rapidly.
In 1968 the Reston Community Association (RCA) was created to take responsibility for community programs. The RCA's first program was the establishment of the Commuter Express Bus System in March of 1968. The Reston Home Owner Association was created in 1970 by consolidating the original First and Second Home Owner Associations that had been established in 1963. The new RHOA was given also in 1970 the deeds of recreational facilities by the Reston Gulf, Inc. These facilities included Lake Anne, swimming pools, parks and bridges. The Reston Home Owner Association was later renamed the Reston Association in 1987. Today the Reston Association is run by the Board of Directors and several committees and continues to be in charge of designs, covenant for Reston properties, maintaining the open space areas within Reston, and recreational and educational programs for all ages in Reston.
Scope and Content
The Reston Association records include meeting minutes, budgets, clippings, reports, handbooks, correspondence, and general information on the association. Also included is a series of photography, which has photographs, contact sheets, slides, and negatives. The collection documents the activities of the Reston Home Owners Association, later renamed Reston Association in 1987 to include apartments and condos. The collection covers the period of time from the 1964 to 2006.
Series 1 includes correspondence dated from 1969 to 1997. The letters include information about different meetings, elections and invitations. The correspondence deals with the Reston Association and various aspects of the running of the association. The memos cover a variety of topics that the Reston Association was responsible for including pathways, membership and even cable television in 1985.
Series 2 is titled Director's Files and relate to Dan McGuire and the Reston Home Owner Coalition from the mid-1980s. The papers are from a variety of sources including meeting agendas, personal correspondence and notes. The Coalition appears to be a competing association within the Reston Home Owner Association from a dispute within Reston. The series also includes information on the All-American City which is related to the Reston Home Owner Coalition because the paperwork also deals with Dan McGuire.
Series 3 contains the minutes from different meetings, primarily council, committee and board of directors' meetings. The minutes record those people who were present at the meeting and the information that discuss during it. This is the largest series of paperwork in the Reston Association collection. It has 168 folders in 4 boxes, the folders are dated from 1972-2004.
Series 4 is titled Reports, the documents provided the associations with updates and information on various projects and programs within Reston, such as land use, homeless and a large portion are financial reports submitted to the association in 1990. Also mixed in the series are the RHOA Plus White Papers created by a committee to help increase membership at the community recreational facilities in Reston. The papers in this series are the information the committee submitted to the association in March of 1981.
Series 5 concerns the budget. The folders are dated from 1969 to 1995. The information outlines the budget for various projects and programs such as recreation. The series also includes assessments of the budget from various months during the 1980s and 1990s. This series is also large and is stored in 5 boxes.
Series 6 consists of paperwork from different Reston committees. Subjects that this series covers includes education, elections, health care and other issues. Also included is information from planning and zoning of Reston. The series is dated from 1969 to 2000.
Series 7 consists of articles relating to Reston. The articles cover a variety of topics such as elections, grand openings, community newsletters, and other community functions. The articles are from papers from The Connection, a local Fairfax newspaper, The Washington Post and other publications. The series is dated from 1964-2005.
Series 8 consists of handbooks and other manuals. The files includes recommendations, RHOA handbooks and other manuals about the operations and procedures of the Reston Association different projects and programs. The information in the handbooks covers a variety of topics including membership studies, covenant and design regulations for Reston.
Series 9 contains files and is entitled General Information. The information is from a various projects and programs that the Association was involved in, such as maintenance, volunteer programs in the community, annual reports and information about the board. This series also includes articles dealing with problems in the Reston Association. Topics covered by the articles include corruption within the Association and changes that occurred because of the problems.
Series 10 consists of photographs, slides, contact sheets, negatives and videos. Most of the images document programs run by the Reston Association. Some of the programs shown in this series are summer camps, which includes day, nature, swim and tennis, for children and senior movie day. There are also larger items in oversize cases. These items appear to be for display purposes at different Reston community facilities. This series is dated earlier and later than any other series in this collection. The images date from 1969 to 2004.
Arrangement
Organized into 10 series.
Series 1: Correspondence, 1969-1997 (Boxes 1-6)
Series 2: Director's Files, 1980-1986 (Boxes 6-7)
Series 3: Minutes, 1972-2004 (Boxes 7-13)
Series 4: Reports, 1962-2005 (Boxes 13-20)
Series 5: Budget, 1969-1995 (Boxes 20-25)
Series 6: Committee, 1969-2000 (Boxes 25-27)
Series 7: Articles, 1964-2005 (Boxes 27-29)
Series 8: Handbooks, 1965-2005 (Boxes 29-33)
Series 9: General Information, 1966-2006 (Boxes 33-41)
Series 10: Photographs, 1969-2004 (Boxes 41-54)
Adjunct Descriptive Data
Related Material
The Special Collections and Archives also holds the Planned Community Archives and other personal papers and organizational records that document Reston, Virginia and other planned communities.
Index Terms
Persons:
Simon, Robert E. (Robert Edward), 1914-
Corporate Names:
Reston Association.
Geographical Names:
Reston (Va.)
Subjects:
Housing.; Planned communities.
Document Types:
Photographic negatives.; Photographic prints.; Slides.
Contents List
- Series 1: Correspondence, 1969-1997; (6 boxes)
  The Correspondence Series has folders. The letters include information about different meetings, elections and invitations. The correspondence deals with the Reston Association and various aspects of the running of the association. All of the correspondence is dated from 1969-1997.
  - Administration, Operation and Personnel, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    509.26
  - Apartment Owner, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    437.9
  - Board Administration Committee (BAC), 1989 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    426.29
  - Board Administration Committee (BAC), 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    428.24
  - Board of Directors-Legal Committee, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    427.1
  - Board of Directors, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    428.32
  - Board of Directors, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    428.30
  - Board of Directors, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    428.28
  - Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    427.27
  - Board of Directors, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    427.15
  - Board of Directors, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    427.23
  - Board of Directors-Committee and Liaison Assignments, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    426.6
  - Board of Supervisors-Recommendation on Disclosure of Block Votes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    509.20
  - Board Policy, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    509.29
  - Chronological Letter File: July-December, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    1.16
  - Chronological Letter Files, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    1.15
    - Reston Community Association Interim Bylaws, undated; 1.
  - Chronological Letter File, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    1.14
  - Chronological Letter, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    2.02
  - Chronological Letter File: January-June, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    2.05
  - Chronological Memos File July-December, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    2.06
  - Chronological Memos File, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    2.03
  - Chronological Memos File January-June, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 3)
    2.04
  - Chronological Memos, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 4)
    2.01
  - Chronological Memos, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    1.17
  - Civic Association Information, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    535.18
  - Cable Television, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    437.6
  - Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 8)
    435.9
  - Correspondence-Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    435.8
  - Correspondence with The Connection and Complaints, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    537.15
  - County of Fairfax-Complaints and Issues, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    537.3
  - CURE, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    426.13
  - Decision of the Elections Committee, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    509.24
  - Documents, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    439.9
  - Documents, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    439.11
  - Emta-Garage, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 8)
    526.8
  - Lakes Access and Usage, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
    440.3
  - Lake Anne Revitalization Memo from Robert E. Simon to Ruth Overton and Susan Jones, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 10)
    16.19
  - Letter of Transmittal Herndon-Reston Recreation Task Force, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 11)
    536.14
  - Licensing Agreements, 1980s (Box 3, Folder 12)
    440.13
  - Martha, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 13)
    537.12
  - Media General, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 14)
    425.50
  - Membership, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    435.1
  - Membership, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 16)
    435.2
  - Membership, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 17)
    435.3
  - Memorandum-Reception Reminder, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    509.19
  - Memos on Proposed Lake Anne Arts Center, 1998 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    16.20
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 20)
    509.37
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 21)
    509.35
  - Miscellaneous, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    426.25
  - Miscellaneous, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    427.16
  - Miscellaneous, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    528.9
  - Miscellaneous, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 2)
    537.18
  - Miscellaneous Treasurer, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    529.9
  - north Nature Center, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    436.9
  - Park and Ride, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    527.20
  - Pathways, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    436.13
  - Personal, 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Power Outages Surveys, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    527.21
  - President (RAC), 1976-1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    529.13
  - Proposal for Developing a Marketing Communication, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    436.8
  - Racquet Club, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    509.34
  - Redevelopment, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    527.17
  - Referendum Considerations, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    427.11
  - Reston Beautification, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    437.3
  - Reston Community Association, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 15)
    530.13
  - Reston Community Association, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 16)
    530.14
  - Reston Community Association, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    525.3
  - Reston Community Association, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    527.32
  - Reston Community Association, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    530.2
  - Reston Community Association, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    530.5
  - Reston Community Association, 1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    530.6
  - Reston Community Association, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    530.12
  - Reston Governance Task Force, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    436.7
  - Reston Homeowners Association (RHOA), 1985 (Box 5, Folder 6)
    440.5
  - Reston Homeowners Association Facilities Usage, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    509.27
  - Reston Internal Bus System, 1985 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    436.6
  - Reston Land Corporation, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    440.10
  - Reston Land Corporation, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    440.4
  - Sheraton Site, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    527.14
  - Sheraton Site, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    527.15
  - Sheraton Site, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    527.16
  - Sister City-Reston and Nyeri, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    527.13
  - Springfield By-pass, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    527.12
  - State Corporate Commission, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    527.10
  - Streetlights, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    527.8
  - Streetlights, 1983 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    527.7
  - Swing, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    442.10
  - Telephone Confirmation, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    509.32
  - Thank You Letters, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 9)
    537.8
  - Unplanned Power Outage Issues, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    537.2
  - Volleyball Courts, 1985 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    436.11
- Series 2: Director's Files, 1980-1986; (1.5 boxes)
  These 24 folders are from Dan McGuire relating to the Reston Home Owner Coalition from the mid-1980s. The papers are from a variety of sources including meeting agendas and correspondence. The series also includes information on the All-American City which is related to the Reston Home Owner Coalition.
  - All American City, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    442.3
    - Letter: William G. Andersen, Jr. and Debra J. Collins, October 2, 1986; 1.
    - Paper: Citizens Forum on Self-Government/National Municipal League, Inc., 1986; 2.
  - All American City, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 13)
    443.14
  - All American City, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 14)
    443.15
  - All American City, 1980s (Box 6, Folder 15)
    443.16
  - All American City, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 1)
    442.5
    - Letter: John Parr and Allison Moore, 26 May 1988; 1.
    - Newsletter: National Civic League, "Civic Action", July/August 1992; 2.
  - All American City, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 2)
    442.4
  - All American City, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    442.2
  - All American City, 1982 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    442.1
  - Board of Directors-Miscellaneous Issues, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    434.4
  - Dan McGuire Personal Correspondence, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 6)
    442.8
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition-Recreation, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 7)
    443.13
    - Entry form: Charles D. McGuire, 1988/89; Letter from Charles D. McGuire to All-America City Program, 31 March 1989; 1.
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    443.1
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 9)
    443.2
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 10)
    443.3
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 11)
    443.4
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    443.5
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 13)
    443.6
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    443.7
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
    443.8
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 16)
    443.9
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 17)
    443.10
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition-Correspondence, 1980s-1990s (Box 7, Folder 18)
    443.11
  - Dan McGuire Reston Homeowners Coalition-Public Housing, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 19)
    443.12
  - Issues, 1980s (Box 7, Folder 20)
    437.2
  - Personal Letters, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    442.7
- Series 3: Minutes, 1972-2004; (7 boxes)
  This large series includes 168 folders. All the folders contain the minutes from different meetings, such as council and board of directors. The information included in the minutes is who was present at the meeting and the information that discuss during it. The folders are dated from 1972 to 2004.
  - Agenda, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    427.12
  - Agenda, 2004 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Annual Meeting of Members, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    426.32
  - Annual Meeting of Members, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    426.4
  - Annual Meeting of Members, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    427.46
  - Annual Meeting-Board of Directors, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 1)
    426.5
  - Board of Directors-Agenda, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 2)
    427.13
  - Board of Directors Annual Meeting, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 3)
    427.47
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 4)
    427.45
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 5)
    428.1
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 6)
    428.2
  - Board of Directors Agenda, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 7)
    428.3
  - Board of Directors Fiscal Committee, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 8)
    428.4
  - Board of Directors-Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    428.6
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 10)
    428.8
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 11)
    428.10
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 8, Folder 12)
    428.11
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 13)
    428.13
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 14)
    428.14
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 15)
    428.15
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 16)
    428.16
  - Board of Directors Special Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 17)
    428.17
  - Board of Directors Special Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 19)
    428.19
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 20)
    428.20
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 21)
    428.22
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 22)
    428.23
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 23)
    428.25
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 24)
    428.26
  - Board of Directors Board Administration Committee, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 25)
    428.27
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1992 (Box 8, Folder 26)
    428.29
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 27)
    428.31
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 28)
    428.34
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 29)
    428.35
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 30)
    428.36
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 31)
    428.37
  - Board of Directors Special Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 32)
    428.38
  - Board of Directors, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 33)
    428.39
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 34)
    428.40
  - Board of Directors, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 35)
    428.41
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 36)
    426.24
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 37)
    426.26
  - Board of Directors-Minutes, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 38)
    426.27
  - Board of Directors-Minutes, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 39)
    426.31
  - Board of Directors Annual Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 1)
    426.33
  - Board of Directors Retreat, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    426.34
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 3)
    427.2
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 4)
    427.3
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    427.4
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 6)
    427.5
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 7)
    427.6
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 8)
    427.7
  - Board of Directors, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 9)
    427.8
  - Board of Directors Personnel Committee, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    427.9
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 11)
    427.10
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1989 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    427.14
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 13)
    427.19
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 14)
    427.18
  - Board of Directors Public Hearing, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 15)
    427.20
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 16)
    427.21
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 17)
    427.22
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 18)
    427.24
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 19)
    427.26
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 20)
    427.30
  - Board of Directors Board and Staff Retreat, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 21)
    427.28
  - Board of Directors Agenda, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 22)
    427.31
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 23)
    427.32
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 24)
    427.33
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 25)
    427.34
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 26)
    427.35
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 27)
    427.36
  - Board of Directors Public Hearing, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 28)
    427.37
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
    427.39
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
    427.43
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1991 (Box 9, Folder 31)
    427.44
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 32)
    426.2
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 33)
    426.9
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 34)
    426.12
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 35)
    426.14
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 36)
    426.15
  - Board of Directors Design Review Board-Agenda, 1988 (Box 9, Folder 37)
    426.16
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    426.17
  - Board of Directors-Program and Plus Services Advisory Committee, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    426.18
  - Board of Directors-Personnel Committee, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 3)
    426.19
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 4)
    426.20
  - Board of Directors-Budget Work Session, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    426.21
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    426.22
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes (Draft), 1985 (Box 10, Folder 7)
    425.31
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    425.32
  - Board of Directors Meeting Minutes, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    425.33